http://www.talktofrank.com/privacy_policy

Skip to main contentPrivacy policyThis website is an independent government funded website maintained for your personal use and viewing. Access and use by you of this website constitutes acceptance by you of these terms and conditions that take effect from the date of first use.All correspondence with FRANK is held in the strictest confidence. Your personal information and conversation with FRANK will not be shared or re-used without your prior consent. Whatever you say to FRANK privately is respected and goes no further.
FRANK is fully committed to ensuring the privacy of website users. This Privacy Policy Statement explains how we use your personal information to improve the service we can offer you. This policy may change occasionally so please check this statement from time to time.What information we collectWe collect personal information from you through any enquiry forms that you complete and through any e-mails or text messages that you send us.We also collect information automatically each time you visit the site. This information, which includes parts of the site visited, is only used as aggregate information, not as individual information.What we do with personal informationWe use personal information that you give us to answer your enquiries, and provide you with information you have requested.We also use the aggregate information about visitors' site usage patterns to enable us to see how popular different parts of the site are with our visitors, helping us decide how best to further develop the site.Who do we share information with?We will not share any information we store about you with any third party, except for suppliers or referral agencies we use to provide services that require them to process data for us.
